[ghostly exhale]
[film reel clattering]
[synth notes]
[thunder rolling]
[dramatic instrumental music]
[ethereal tones]
[click]
[soft vocalizing]
Dearest Peggy.
Please let me go.
[soft vocalizing]
[soft music continues]
You have no power here.
[Man] This is all in the cavers
of our minds.
[evil laughter]
[Woman] Yeah, I would love to,
James, that sounds great.
[James] Oh, that's so awesome.
That's so awesome.
Okay, great.
Um, I can pick you up at 7:00?
[Man] This is mom's
newest movie.
Got the new movie poster up?
Yes. Do you like it?
[laughs]
What the hell?
The Mummy?
[Narrator] Marilyn Lee Miller's
career is going to be facing
an uphill battle after
the last low budget snoozefest
has underperformed
at the box office.
No surprise there.
It's terrible.
[Narrator] We're
hearing in the press
the B-movie actress
is planning to retire to spend
more time with her son.
Sure, Marilyn. Your retirement
has nothing to do with
the utter garbage
you've been starring in
with these last few movies.
Do people still watch
these indie films?
They're a cancer
to the industry.
What a drag,
and what a waste of time.
I think we need to take a long,
hard look at these movies
and see if they have a place
in a civilized society.
[ethereal vocalization]
[screaming]
[Man] Mom! Oh, shit.
Please. No!
What did you do?
[soft music continues]
[Narrator] People still watch
these indie films?
They're a cancer
to the industry.
Are they creating
real life monsters?
[voice echoes]
[sinister music]
Luuucy!
[Man] Chop to the bitch,
chop to the boy!
Chop 'til
the body's destroyed!
[Woman] For the love of God,
please stop!
[Man] I'm dying.
[Woman] Oh, God! Oh!
[Boy] Where do we go?
Colin.
Dinner's almost ready
if you want to join us.
Colin?
[sinister music]
[Man] Ronnie!
Where are you?
Wanna play hide and seek?
- [gunshot]
- [man groaning]
[indistinct chanting together]
[together] Just like I said.
[screaming]
Did you enjoy that?
I've seen that movie 13 times,
and I'm starting to hate it.
This is Doctor Dementia,
your ever faithful servant.
Serving you the best way I--
What's he doing?
Same as always. Watching
Marilyn's old scary movies.
That kid is obsessed.
Now you know I told you
we needed to make other
arrangements for him.
The hell was I supposed
to do, Patricia?
I mean, we're the only
family he's got left.
I know you felt obligated
because of your sister,
but there's just something
really off about him.
He's- I don't know, he's--
He's cracked,
and he's a fucking freak.
Kasie, language.
Excuse me for
speaking the truth.
Maybe he just misses his mom.
Yeah. Thank you,
Captain Obvious.
That still doesn't change
the fact that he's creepy.
Did you tell your father about
the little mishap the other day?
What mishap?
I came home to find
my underwear drawer open.
Someone had been
going through it.
The little creepo was
probably sniffing her panties.
Yeah, and that's not all.
I swear I caught him staring at
me in the shower this morning.
And I've caught him
in my room multiple times,
just standing over me,
watching me sleep.
Yeah. Me too.
It's all of those
movies he watches.
Come on.
Just because he's obsessed
with scary movies
[scoffs] doesn't mean
he's some sort of psycho.
Just give him a motel and he's
practically Norman Bates.
[ominous piano notes]
Why do you still
have your costume on?
Logan. Shh.
Let's eat everyone.
This chili smells funny.
Eat it, brat.
It smells... different.
[Patricia] Just eat your
peanut butter sandwich, Logan.
Colin, you should eat something.
[Bennett] You're just going
to stare at it?
Okay.
[sinister music increases]
Bennett?
[dramatic sting]
[music intensifies]
[gagging]
[retching]
[vomiting]
Mom?
Son of a bitch!
[sinister music continues]
[music intensifies]
[thudding and squelching]
[thud]
[screaming on tv]
[Man] How dare you try
to leave me?
[squelching]
[movie continues]
[thud]
[Woman] I called them.
Please just let me go
right now!
[wincing]
[voice whispering] Colin...
[whispering]
Colin, this isn't you!
[voice whispering] My boy...
[Detective]
End of the line, Rondo.
We know you committed
those murders.
You're not going to
hurt anybody else,
you ice cream fuck!
Attention!
I got a little
prescription for you.
Come on, here.
Close. Close, close, close.
You know we're just
getting started.
[voice whispering] Kill...
[heavy thudding]
[Eleanor screaming]
[Announcer] We'll be right back
with more Doctor Dementia
and our double creature feature
on channel 18 superstation.
[sinister music]
[door creaking]
I wish I could make it stop.
No matter what, I...
I can't bring her back.
Ironic.
Isn't it?
She made scary movies.
Now I'm...
making my own.
When they stare into the dark
from this moment forward...
they'll see me.
You'll see me, too.
I'll come back for you.
[tense music]
[music intensifies]
If you don't like this movie,
I don't know how
I can help you.
[rock music]
♪ And I'm out the door ♪
♪ Live the high life
I've been waiting for ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Got no home,
ain't got no name ♪
♪ Changin' my view
again and again ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
[Woman] Louis C. Gallegos. Hmm.
♪ Live in the moment
till I die ♪
[Radio] You're listening
to 102.1.
I am running ragged today.
Bingo hall keeping you
up late again, huh?
[laughs sarcastically]
Is that your fourth
cup of coffee?
Six, actually.
Are you, uh, still going
to this Grave Rave thing?
It appears I am.
Scooby gang is making me.
- Uh-huh.
- [phone ringing]
Vortex Video.
[Woman] Do you have Marilyn Lee
Miller's "Lewisville"?
Nope. Sorry. We're out.
[hangs up]
[sighs]
What's got you all spazzed out?
Oh, just this time of year.
October hits, and it's
Marilyn Lee Miller this
and Marilyn Lee Miller that.
Yeah, well, our town is known
for a B-movie scream queen
offing herself, so.
Yeah.
What is that?
I don't know.
Got some guy from "Night of
the Living Dead" in it.
Oh. Very cool.
Yeah. I've been waiting
for Romero
to make a new zombie flick.
I think "The Crazies" was a lot
scarier than "Night" or "Dawn".
Okay. Blasphemy.
But to each their own, I guess.
70's and 80's were
the golden age of horror.
Yeah, they don't make 'em
like they used to.
Even though you take
them way too seriously.
Horror movies are life, okay?
- It's--
- Oh, god.
It's like, about releasing
your fears and facing them.
People are empowered by...
facing their real life bullshit.
Yeah. Can you just stop it
with all that shit?
It's true.
You know, can we just
keep movies as an escape?
The best horror movies
have something to say.
The best movies,
including horror,
- suspend reality.
- Okay.
People need to shut up
and eat their popcorn.
No. How can you watch
"I Spit on Your Grave"
or "The Hills Have Eyes"
and think it's an escape.
Because it's a movie.
It's not real!
Hmm. Okay.
Well, Grandma, what kind
of movies do you like?
Um...
"The Howling" was really good.
The original,
not the porno sequels.
- That's fair.
- You know,
people watch movies
for the same reason
they go on rollercoasters.
The thrill should be fun.
- [door bell rings]
- [Big Dan] Heya, cookies!
Oh, boy.
Hey, toots.
What does that even mean?
This is the 90's, not the 40's.
The 90's suck.
Give me gangsters, bootleggers,
and the jitterbug.
Ain't that right, Gran-Gran?
Big Gran-Gran to you.
I think I'm gonna stick with
the right to vote in Nintendo.
Hey, my beautiful ladies.
Guys, I love the costumes.
Beka, you look stunning.
Thank you.
And Big Dan, you're...
Richard Simmons?
Yeah. I don't know who that is.
I'm a vintage
fitness instructor.
Right. Richard Simmons.
Yeah.
Quinn, where's your costume?
We got to get out of here.
We have so many
epic things planned.
You guys keep alluding
to that,
but I don't know
what's going on.
In the words of Pinhead,
"we have such sights
to show you".
Okay.
- Bye.
I love you.
[Sybil] Love you.
Have fun guys.
[Man] Load their men
onto the dock.
[Quinn] Where is the rest
of this gang?
You know, doing stuff.
Working on things.
Yeah. I'm not really
a fan of the surprise.
Whatever it is.
Well, I personally plan to be
higher than a fruit fly on kiwi.
Okay.
Look, I have enough weed to kill
a small-- ah, it's a cop!
Oh.
- Hey, Logan.
- Hey, Beka.
- Quinn.
- Hey.
Big Dan.
Officer Miller.
Officer Logan?
Logan Miller. My dude.
[Big Dan] Okay.
What are you doing?
I'm just getting ready to
head in and start my shift.
By the looks of it, you guys
are headed to the event.
We are.
Cool. Now then, I...
guess I'll see you around
at some point tonight.
Yeah.
So fun.
We have to get the Princess
of Punctuality ready.
So, bye Lo.
[Logan] Yeah.
Hey, you guys, be safe.
So awkward.
Yeah, he's like a real life
final boy.
He's lived through
a horror movie.
That too.
That was one time.
Two times.
Yeah. Officer Miller
needs a little bit of...
this and a little bit of that.
Right, Quinn?
You're disgusting.
What'd I say? Am I wrong?
What did I say?
[Beka] You're buying
the first round.
[rock guitar notes]
[Radio] Carpenter falls is back
from the dead tonight
as we pay tribute
to our haunted past
with the first ever Grave Rave!
[heavy rock music]
[Radio] That's right.
The ghouls are around
and the ghosts are rocking
as we celebrate
spooky season in style.
[crowd cheering]
♪ To the one and only ♪
[cheering]
Grave Rave in the house!
♪ Darkness of the night,
years ago ♪
♪ Television memories ♪
If he keeps giving away
free drinks over here,
we're not going to
make any money tonight.
Oh, man, I gave up
trying to talk sense
into that boy years ago.
Come on.
Hey, how's it hanging, Harp?
Hanging pretty
low at the moment.
What's up?
Why is the police department
here drinking
instead of doing their duties?
Hey, you know what?
Everybody here is trying
to have a good time, okay?
Don't you start,
you'll make like a mess.
Don't do that, Harp.
I'm just saying, though.
Hey hey hey hey hey.
Can we get a beer?
A beer or something?
Why don't you take that
and cool your tits?
♪ Immortal apathy ♪
♪ Takes her
her down with him ♪
♪ In the darkness
of the night ♪
♪ There is a glow ♪
♪ Television memories
and videos ♪
[rock music concludes]
How's everyone doing tonight?
[crowd cheering]
Welcome to the first,
and certainly not the last,
Grave Rave event here
in Carpenter Falls.
[cheering]
We want to thank Julia.
- Thank you.
- [cheering]
I'd like to thank
the Pioneer Playhouse
and the Marilyn Lee Miller
Museum for hosting this event.
[cheering]
Now, without further ado,
please join me
in welcoming our very own
Erin Palmer!
[cheering and applause]
Let's talk Halloween.
For most people,
they grow up scared
of ghosts and boogeymen.
It's not the same
for us in Carpenter Falls.
30 years ago, B-movie scream
queen and our hometown hero,
Marilyn Lee Miller,
took her own life,
thus sending her only
child into madness and insanity.
The 15 year old then went on to
murder his uncle's entire family
before disappearing
into the night forever.
[Julia] Don't believe me?
The only living survivor
from that horrific slaying
is here tonight.
Mr. Logan Miller.
[scattered applause]
[Julia] After that night,
Colin Miller ceased to exist.
[tense, unsettling music]
And the legend of
the Boy from Below was born.
[haunting vocalizing]
Beware the Boy from Below.
[crowd] The sad, tormented,
vengeful soul.
[crowd] You may see him,
you might.
His curse will continue
on Halloween night.
Happy Halloween everyone.
[cheering and applause]
Cheers. All of us.
[hard rock music plays]
That was epic as hell, babe.
Thanks, babe.
Mhm.
[Big Dan] Oh, yes, mami.
Why don't you take me
back to your van
and whisper
sweet nothings into my ear?
Ignore him.
Big Dan's just salty
because Heather won't
give him the time of day.
And you can extra
salty deez nuts.
I'm so done with you.
- No you're not.
- That's true.
[Quinn] So what's the 411
on the surprise?
And if it's Big Dan
spiking my drink,
then I think we're all
in for a surprise tonight.
[Julia] Trust me.
Your friends thought
this night was long overdue, so
we cooked up a little something
something for you.
Cheers to that.
And to Quinn having
a social life again.
Woo!
Why is everyone so obsessed
with my social life?
I mean...
Maybe because you don't
actually have one?
Bro.
Uh, I'm gonna use the restroom.
Oh.
You. Not nice.
Facts don't care
about your feelings.
Sorry, guys.
Some fucker at the bar
was talking my ear off
trying to pick me up.
Seriously almost
blew my rape whistle.
Oh, that's Harper.
He's always smelled like
tequila and Drakkar Noir to me.
[Erin] He's fine
when he's sober.
Hold up. I'm still stuck
on this rape whistle.
Like, is that a real thing?
What?
Do not blow that.
I got something she can blow.
- Stop it.
- Beka.
You know, I must say,
your costume is an improvement
from last year's.
Remember, you wore the little
plaid skirt and we thought
you looked like Velma
from Scooby Doo?
Contrary to your
point of view,
Halloween isn't exactly
an excuse to dress up like...
a dirty slut.
Awe.
Thank you.
See you guys.
- Cheers.
Officer.
- Hey, fellas.
- My man.
Get your skinny ass-
Sit down.
Have a drink with us.
Come on.
How do you put up with this?
I've been doing it
my whole life.
I grew up with this
kid right here.
Sit down. One drink.
You're being rude.
Come on. Pop a squat.
So, uh, how's life
at the marina?
It's quiet.
Still on the houseboat?
[laughing]
Yeah, I am.
What's wrong?
You look like-
You look like
you've seen a ghost.
He does this all the time,
tearing up.
I bet you right now
his hands are so moist,
he can't even pick up
that goddamn beer.
[laughing] Knock it off.
Knock it off.
You don't have to
take that from him.
It's fine, Chief.
I'm used to it.
All right. Okay.
All right. Listen.
I know Halloween, it's a bit
of a trigger point for you.
I'm just trying to bring
a little bit of levity
to the situation, all right?
Maintaining composure
is a part of what we do.
You are literally the opposite
of composure, Goodman.
The fuck does that mean?
It means you're a bull
in a fucking china shop.
[laughs]
All right, all right, look.
I'm about to go say goodbye
to my little girl over there,
and call it an evening.
And you two.
don't start any fires
that I'm going to have
to put out tomorrow.
Copy that.
Night, Chief.
All right.
Chug chug chug!
Chug chug chug chug!
[chanting continues]
Who is this chick?
I told you, she's dope!
You weren't lying.
How long was that?
Somebody took time?
I went to five...
I'm getting that twice.
Somebody's gotta pay up.
[Cooper] Well, well.
Would you look who we have here?
[Quinn] Cooper. Jojo.
How are you?
How's it going, hot stuff?
[Cooper] Let me ask you
something, Quinn.
How come we've never...
hooked up?
Must be your winning
personality, you know? Just...
too much for me to bear.
Ever have a three way?
Phone call?
Yeah. You guys have fun.
Whoa whoa whoa.
You know what I think is funny?
You run around here covering
those rotten ass tattoos,
acting like society
owes you something,
and it's all just
a desperate cry for attention.
Here I am, giving you
the chance to slob on my knob,
and you're turning me down.
Come on, man, you ain't got
the right equipment, bro.
She's playing for
the other team.
I can change that.
[Max] Hey! Fuck off!
Get lost, bitch.
You think I don't
know what you are?
I don't give a fuck
what you know.
Imagine what everyone will say
about you after I'm done
kicking your ass and shattering
your fragile ego.
You're gonna leave
Quinn alone,
or I'll handle you
and dumb fuck over there.
[Logan] Is everything cool
over here?
Yeah. Peachy.
Never been better.
I was just telling Max here
that I'm so glad
she's back in town,
and I'll be
seeing her around.
Come on, dude,
let's get out of here.
Hey, Quinn.
It's been a minute.
♪ Let me tell you ♪
Are you fucking kidding me?
♪ I have all the reasons
to hate him ♪
Wait.
♪ But you know what? ♪
Dude. Who the fuck
is the new girl?
It's Max.
Where'd you get the pizza?
♪ Feels like this,
feels like this ♪
It's true.
Everybody's thinking it.
[laughing]
Oh, guys,
Quinn's coming this way
and she looks pissed.
Shit.
I want to go back
to the video store.
Excuse me.
Now.
Quinn.
♪ You're done ♪
♪ Don't go ♪
You guys didn't tell
her I was coming?
Not really.
We wanted it to be a surprise.
Well, fuck, Dan! The only
surprise is that your brain
doesn't fall out your ass
when you take a shit!
[Big Dan] How is this my fault?
[Max] Argh!
♪ Stop laughing ♪
♪ Stop crying ♪
♪ Don't do anything ♪
[Radio]...pizza, the best pies
in Carpenter Falls.
Carryout or delivery available.
Oh, hi.
Oh. Into the scary stuff, huh?
Yeah. I can't wait
to watch these.
Yeah, my granddaughter
loves these, too.
This stuff doesn't scare you?
That's kind of the point.
Point taken.
Uh. Let's see.
Here we go.
- There you go.
- Thank you.
Oh, well, thank you, sir.
And... be safe.
I will. Thanks.
- Thank you.
- You bet. Bye.
[sighs]
Okay.
You've been looking
at this shelf for a while now.
There something I can help you
find before we have to close?
Sorry. Just a little indecisive.
No problem. Let me see.
You strike me as a man who
loves action and horror,
but only horror
if it's story driven.
Oh. Don't ask. It's a gift.
Um,
this is the one for you.
Right on the money.
Mhm. Solid story.
Really thrilling action
sequences and good suspense.
And the actors
that play the couple?
Really great chemistry.
Well I'm sold.
Check it out.
Is it a love story?
Oh, I think you'll dig it.
Okay, we're heading to a
cabin with some friends.
Figured we'd pick
something up, so.
- Yeah.
- Fine.
We're good?
This is what the lady says.
I think we should listen.
All right.
I'll catch you at the counter.
- Finally. Thank you.
- Shut up.
[foreboding music]
I promise you.
I'll be gentle.
[bar chatter]
[tv] After her!
[Jojo] Remind me again.
Why am I here?
[Cooper] Because you suck
at fending off peer pressure.
Those lesbians have me
so fucking pissed off.
I just need to release some
of this pent up frustration.
Do you ever wonder
what it's like?
[Cooper] What?
Hook up with a dude?
Why would you think that?
Are you some sort of fag?
- No!
- Hey.
Hey, eyes up here.
You better not be
checking out my ass.
Go!
[Jojo] Sorry, bucko.
We didn't see you there.
Oh, shit.
He's digging up
that Marilyn Miller.
Hey.
What the hell do you
think you're doing here?
[Cooper] I'm talking to you,
Chewbacca.
[tense music]
- [thud]
- [Cooper groans]
[dramatic music]
[squelch]
[blood spurting]
No! No!
[Cooper] Leave me alone!
I want to go home!
No!
No! Just want to go home!
[groaning]
[screaming]
[haunting vocalizing]
[ominous, dramatic music]
Twisted Turbo,
available everywhere, now!
Welcome back to late night
horror theater.
[woman screaming on tv]
[Man] Woo!
[knocking]
So I guess our plan didn't go
as well as we all had hoped?
You knew about this?
I might have had a hand in it.
Unbelievable.
I can't trust anybody.
Hey, we all just want
what's best for you.
You think someone abandoning
me is what's best for me?
Okay, Moody Blues.
I understand why
you're angry at Max.
It was shitty how
she just took up and left.
But give her an
opportunity to explain.
Why should I?
Quinn.
you don't have
to pretend with me.
I saw how close
the two of you were.
Okay, well, her leaving
negated any feelings.
Okay? Why can't she just
tell me why she did it?
If I could play devil's
advocate here for just a minute.
I remember both of you
dreaming of a life outside
of Carpenter Falls.
Well, some of us have
responsibilities.
Oh, honey, please.
Please. You mean you want
to live with this old broad
and run a video store
the rest of your life?
Come on, Grandma.
All I'm saying is just...
don't make a decision
out of anger.
Those usually can't be undone.
Can't play it safe
all your life, sweetie.
[exhales]
[foreboding music]
Well, somebody missed out.
Last night's Grave Rave
was a smash hit.
Great!
There are so many ways
we can capitalize on the legacy
of Marilyn Lee Miller.
And this is just the beginning!
I'm thinking we should
do something
with the old Miller property.
I mean, look what Graceland has
done for the city of Memphis.
Millions and millions
in added tax revenue.
International
tourist destination.
I'm thinking that old property
could be Carpenter Falls'
Graceland.
Looks like you've got it all
figured out, Mayor Bloomberg.
Well, yeah.
I mean, people from all over
would come to experience
the rich history
of a silver screen legend.
And you know what that means?
Thank you.
Do you know what that means?
That means that your little
video store over here
could experience
big business, too.
Oh, well, that would
be interesting.
Yes. Very interesting.
Yeah, I agree, I'm about to
go over to Julia's right now
and work out all the details.
This town needs
a boost like this!
- [phone vibrating]
- Excuse me.
My cellular phone is vibrating.
Bloomberg.
Hey, Alice.
Yeah.
What do you mean,
at the cemetery?
They found what?
Oh, God.
I feel so bad for Logan Miller.
Shit. Show of a family
and now guys like that
are trying to capitalize
on his tragedy.
It's fucked up.
Yeah, well, screw Bloomberg.
He's a slimeball.
[door bell rings]
[rock music plays on radio]
Open heart, open mind.
[Beka] Hey, babe.
Hey.
Are you okay?
We are so sorry.
We just care about you, and...
we wanted to do something
nice for you.
I get it.
Um, yeah. No. I'm sorry.
I kind of flipped my shit
on you guys last night.
So does that mean you don't
want to kill us anymore?
- I think so.
- Quinn?
I just want you to know I had
nothing to do with their plan.
I'm sorry they're stupid.
Anyways.
We messed things up
big time, and--
No, listen. I get it, okay?
It was-
It was a lot of different
emotions, that's all.
But I'll be fine.
You say that a lot.
Like a whole lot.
But we still love you.
And... so does Max.
[tender music]
Where is she?
[Max] If it makes a difference,
I thought you knew I was coming.
I thought...
I thought you wanted me
to be here.
Where did you go, Max?
You just- you left,
and you didn't tell anyone.
I couldn't say anything.
Why not?
Because...
because it was easier that way.
Yeah, easier for you.
It wasn't easy for me. I-
I needed you.
I needed my best friend.
You're right.
I should have told you.
I just wanted to be free of
this place and all the bullshit.
I'm sorry, Quinny.
I guess it is kind of cool,
seeing you.
It's good to see you, too.
I'm sorry I went nuclear on you.
You deserved it, but...
I shouldn't have gone off
on a friend like that.
Ah.
I see.
A friend.
Yeah. You're my oldest friend.
Yeah. To be honest, Quinn,
that was one of the reasons
I had to go.
Being your friend, it wasn't
enough for me anymore.
Yeah, well, I don't know
if I was- or if I'm...
I mean, you have never
had a problem
being who you are, and...
for me,
I'm being all of these different
things for different people,
and I'm tired.
And I just don't have the energy
to be who I need to be for me.
You'd be surprised who and what
I have a problem being.
You're stronger than you
give yourself credit for.
[mellow music]
♪ Messed up, you are ♪
[Erin] They are holding hands.
♪ Like I'm Yoda ♪
♪ You wish we aren't
good company ♪
[Big Dan] Man, I wonder
if they'd let me watch.
[Beka] I shouldn't have
given you the high five.
♪ Make it make sense ♪
[sighs] Oh, wow.
Those are expecting us to...
kiss or something?
Yeah. Big Dan's probably
drooling about it.
♪ Tag along for the ride ♪
♪ Ride ♪
♪ Someone that could
tag along for the ride ♪
♪ Come as you are ♪
♪ We'll listen to your
favorite tune in your car ♪
You guys are so stupid.
For real.
Not you, Miss Sybil.
Awe.
A sight for sore eyes.
You two made up!
So are we ever gonna do this
scary movie thing?
Ooh!
Oh, yes. Boo me.
I'm the bad guy for wanting
to eat popcorn and chillax.
I mean, it was our
Halloween tradition.
Hell, yeah.
Snackages, adult beverages,
adult situations...
Go away, please.
Yeah. And we can pull out
all the classics, too, like um,
"Die! Die! Babe Massacre 4"
and ooh!
"Campground Charlie's Revenge".
Let's watch this one.
It's called
"Don't Fuck in Space".
Who would want to watch this?
I could live without
that last one.
I'd like to save myself
two hours of plot holes.
[Sybil chuckles]
You're coming too, right?
Are you kidding?
I helped start this
tradition with you guys.
I'm so there after I close.
Okay, everybody,
you know the rules.
Everybody gets one pick.
[Erin] Okay, grab your snackies
and let's do this.
♪ I trust my mama ♪
♪ You're no match
for my bad karma ♪
[ominous music]
I don't know how
they got past me.
I was awake all night
in my office
watching reruns
of "Chiller Theater".
Never heard or saw a thing.
Well, those two are notorious
for getting in trouble.
I mean, you know,
it's still just awful.
When I found them...
Wait.
What if that piece of shit
comes back for me?
Calm down.
We don't have any of that
information just yet.
In the meantime,
it'd be a good idea
for you to take a few days off.
Oh, that's really
going to help me.
It will.
Just a few days.
All right.
Well, if that's what you think.
- Thanks, Chief.
- All right. Thank you.
Hey, chief.
I came as soon as I heard.
Yeah.
Poor bastards.
Jojo took a hatchet
to the forehead,
and Cooper
got hollowed out.
Jesus Christ.
Look. I know this is
your family and all,
but do you have any idea
of who would want
to take her body?
Her body?
Marilyn's body.
It's missing.
Somebody dug her up.
[foreboding music]
[threatening piano notes]
[tv] From the outermost
edges of space...
Oh, hold up there,
gang bangers.
We're so gonna die.
Don't lose your shit, Jonesy.
Lieutenant Tate got us through
the Battle of Apex Station.
He'll get us through
this, right Gus?
No doubt, no doubt.
[Erin] Behold
the conquering heroes.
Thanks, babe.
You're the best.
Oh, thank Heather for buying.
Okay. Apparently,
Heather's the best.
Thank you, Heather.
Thanks, Heather.
You're all welcome.
Oh, look at you and your
little chicken nuggies.
Fuck me, that's hot! Mm!
[tv] Get help.
What's that hemorrhoid
looking thing on the wall?
I don't know what it is,
but they've taken out
decks one through nine.
But I promise you,
I'll be getting you guys home
for potatoes and mash.
I'll get y'all--
[Big Dan] This is possibly
the greatest movie ever made.
[Erin] I think you're reaching
with that statement.
Almost as much as you're
reaching for Avery's cock.
Oh, gag me with a spoon.
[Avery] I don't know
about you guys, but
I've had enough of this vagina
frog monster from outer space
bullshit or whatever the hell
it is you've got us watching.
Yeah. I think it's time we
get this party started, huh?
With one from our own
local celebrity
and scream queen herself,
Marilyn Miller?
No!
Her acting is bad, bad.
Uh, this is a masterpiece.
[Erin] Please.
The only thing this has
going for it is the title.
Other than that, it's like...
a rip off of
Friday the 13th and Aliens.
Exactly why I don't watch
stuff like this.
Just cheap imitations
of better shit.
Can we watch something
with a story?
I don't know,
something that's not just
tits, ass, potatoes and mash.
[laughing]
Finally, someone who
shares my taste in movies.
Yeah.
Yeah. I'm sure you share a lot
more than tastes in movies.
Don't worry, Heather,
they're just showing off.
Uh, yeah, because
we're real horror fans.
Being from Carpenter Falls
and all, it's kind of a given.
Dude, look at the tits
on that chick! Oh my god!
Don't listen to him, Heather.
I mean, he clearly only
watches horror for the tits.
So? I like boobs.
Yeah. Who doesn't?
[tv] I was faking it
so hard all night.
Pissed!
[Woman] I'm just saying,
More people disappear
on Halloween
than any other night
of the year.
And it just so happens more
horror movies are rented
on Halloween than any other
time of the year.
[Man] You're not suggesting
horror movies
have something to do
with disappearances.
[Woman] I'm saying we should
take a better look at this.
[Man] Sure, people rent
scary movies and are inspired
to become ax murderers.
[turns power off]
- [thud]
- [yelps]
[Sybil] Uh, I didn't know
anybody was in here.
Uh, sir? I'm- I'm closed.
Maybe you could
come back tomorrow.
[threatening music]
Okay. Uh.
Uh, if you could hurry
and make your selection,
I'll take you up to the counter.
[heavy footsteps]
Ah!
Well.
A Marilyn Lee Miller fan.
Shocker. She was originally
from here, you know.
Okay.
Uh.
[music intensifies]
[music climaxes, fades out]
[Quinn] You don't think
Gremlins is scary?
Or poltergeist?
Dark Crystal ruined
an entire generation.
- Get him, Quinn!
- She likes what she likes.
Maybe "Witches"
or "The Monster Squad"
isn't exactly the blood
fountains that we enjoy,
but, uh, let's not pretend
that "Return to Oz"
didn't completely ruin you.
Fuck "Return to Oz".
Those damn wheelers, man.
No. No, don't even, dude.
[tv] Give me a strawberry
on a cone. Make it fast.
What's that stinky ass
smell in here?
Bad pipes.
[gasping]
[screaming]
[Max] All right,
before we change the movie,
I've got to pee
and take a smoke break.
Uh, yeah.
We should wait on Grammy.
She should be, um,
closing down soon.
[dramatic music]
[whimpers]
[sobbing]
Get away, get away, get away!
[intense synth music]
[Sybil] No, no!
What do you want?!
[screaming]
No!
[soft piano music]
- [Quinn] What are you doing?
- Jesus!
Cool it with that
walking on the wind shit.
You scared me.
Sorry, not sorry.
I was just looking
at the Polaroids,
realizing how much
I missed this.
That's what happens when
you run away from home.
Still giving me shit, huh?
I'm just trying to make sure
that you don't make the biggest
mistake of your life twice.
I'm not going
anywhere without you.
How was it out there?
I wish I could be more
spontaneous like you.
Quinn, you don't have
to be spontaneous.
You just have to live
your life for you.
Doing the things
that you want to do.
Max?
[soft, tender music]
♪ Keep you falling
in circles ♪
♪ In the dark ♪
That's a good start.
♪ Better be careful ♪
♪ Hearts break hard ♪
♪ I got stars in my eyes ♪
♪ Twist you around ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ I'll get you high ♪
♪ Yeah, heaven
is a place we found ♪
♪ Hiding in my energy ♪
Come here.
♪ I got you on your knees
yeah, begging for it ♪
♪ I let you play for keeps ♪
♪ But never play for free ♪
♪ I got you on your knees ♪
♪ Yeah, dying for it ♪
♪ I keep my lover hostage,
I don't work for it ♪
♪ If you want it ♪
♪ Keep my lover hostage ♪
♪ I don't need another
once you got me ♪
[squelching]
♪ Sinkin' into my ocean ♪
♪ Dreams like drugs ♪
♪ One taste,
you'll be hooked ♪
♪ No, you can't get it now ♪
[thud]
♪ Keep my lover hostage ♪
♪ Better work for it
if you want it ♪
♪ Keep my lover hostage ♪
♪ I don't need another
once you've got me hostage ♪
[music fades out]
I love you.
You do?
I love you, too.
[kiss]
[middle eastern music]
[tv] What exactly
brings you to my place?
Looking for someone.
And who would that be?
You'll know soon enough.
Listen, pal.
Where is everyone?
I don't know.
I haven't seen them in a while.
Dan ran after Heather,
and I just assumed that
everybody was getting laid.
Everyone except me.
Uh, Grammy?
That's a negative.
Do you think they all went
down to the video store?
Um, I don't know.
She was supposed to be
off, like, an hour ago.
Oh, shit.
Do you think Dan's
getting her stoned again?
Oh, yeah, for sure he is.
Let's go.
Is that a mummy?
Hey! Hey!
Look over here, Egypt boy!
[mummy snarling]
[ominous music]
Guys?
Cut it out.
I'm not into your
scary movie games.
Those movie suck ass, anyways!
[yelps] Fuck me!
Oh.
Uh. Yes, please?
Seriously? Fuck you, Dan.
Was that you
screwing around with me?
Uh, one, it's Big Dan. And two,
I would love to
screw around with you.
Yeah? Well, the undies
don't lie, small fry.
You're just like
my dipshit brother.
He's always trying to scare me.
Yeah, well, you shouldn't be out
here in the dark by yourself.
There's, like,
raccoons and shit.
What are you doing out here?
I'm protecting you from when
you get scared of the dark.
I'm not scared
of the dark, jerk.
Just the creepy, meepy
assholes wandering around in it.
Come on, Heather.
Don't you think
we should talk about this uh...
What?
This tension between us.
Usually when a guy
tries this hard,
he's still
holding on to his v-card.
Oh, please.
I had a threesome with my
French and Spanish teachers.
I'm tri-lingual.
Well, you're confident
I'll give you that.
Wait, where are you going?
Around.
Little Dan.
[sexy music]
Oh shit.
[sexy, rhythmic beat]
Mami, where are you going?
Don't be shy, Little Dan.
[dramatic sting]
[thud]
[dramatic music]
Come on, little Dan.
Let's see if you have
what it takes to keep up.
[ominous synth music]
Boo!
Sorry, dude.
I thought you were someone else.
Sorry.
Fuck this!
[ominous music continues]
[music fades out]
[dramatic violin strings]
What is Avery and Erin
so long with that pizza?
You know what's
taking them so long.
I don't know why I asked.
What?
Oh, man.
[foreboding music]
What the fuck?
Fuck you.
Okay. What the fuck, dude?
What the fuck?
Okay. Please- please don't-
Please don't--
Stop stop stop stop!
Please, stop stop stop stop!
[saw clatters]
Hold still.
Wait wait wait.
Stop stop stop stop!
Please, stop!
What are you doing?
Dude, stop! Get off me!
[door bell dings]
Grandma?
Grandma! Grandma! Grandma!
Oh, fuck! Grandma!
[Sybil mumbling]
Oh, shit!
[Quinn] Fuck!
What the fuck happened?
Go call for help!
Okay, okay!
[Quinn] Oh, fuck! Fuck! Oh, no!
Oh!
Fuck!
[screaming]
[Big Dan] What the fuck
is your problem?
[Big Dan winces]
[drill whirring]
No, no, no!
Stop stop stop stop stop stop!
[threatening music]
[drill whirring]
[squelching]
[screaming]
[Quinn] Oh, fuck!
The line is dead.
Go to the fucking house!
Grammy!
Get out of here...
No! I don't want to leave you.
- Go!
- I don't want to!
Dan?
[music intensifies]
[Beka gasps]
Dan? Who did this to you?
[Beka wailing]
Okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
Just stay with me, okay?
Dan?
Danny?
[sobbing]
[ominous music]
[metal clanks]
[Beka gasping]
Someone's coming.
Come on. We gotta go.
I don't fucking know.
But we gotta go right now.
Okay. Get up. Get up. Get up.
[Quinn] Come on, Grammy.
Guys.
What the fuck was that?
We need to get out!
Please, Quinn!
- [Quinn] No!
- [Max] Quinn. We have to go.
I know, I know,
but we have to go.
I don't want to!
- [Max] I know. we have to go.
- [Quinn] I don't want to go!
[door creaks]
Hello? Shit!
The line's dead.
Who is he?
Where are the others?
Dan is dead.
[Max] Heather?
Avery? Erin?
Come on, Max.
You watch the same movies as us.
Yeah. They're probably dead.
Fuck.
Okay. Uh, weapons.
Does your grandma
have any in the house?
Um.
- Uh, check her closet.
- Okay.
I know she doesn't
like guns, though.
Do you know how to use a gun?
[cocks gun]
Yes.
Come on.
You ready, babe?
Let's just hang out
for a little bit.
Come on.
You know the gang's waiting.
Besides, we don't want
this pizza to get cold.
I don't want to go back
to that soap opera.
Besides, you know, there was
something I wanted
to do tonight.
Oh, yeah? What's that?
♪ The only reason they
showed up tonight ♪
Are you scared?
No no no no no.
It's just the rain--
Babe. It's okay, don't be--
[gasps and screams]
♪...out of her jacket ♪
[squelching]
[blood spurting]
[screaming]
[synth pop continues playing]
♪ How can I tell you something ♪
No! Please! No!
♪ All I really wanted
was a ride back to your house ♪
[screaming]
No! No!
[squelching]
♪ I know you drove
a shitty car ♪
♪ but you always blasted... ♪
[whimpering and choking]
[Max] It's okay.
Come on, we gotta go.
[twigs snapping]
[Beka] Someone's running.
[leaves rustling]
[footsteps approaching]
- [gunshot]
- [gasp]
[dramatic music increases]
Fuck!
No, no, no, it wasn't him!
It was fucking Heather!
Oh, fuck! Oh!
Holy shit!
Oh, no. Oh, no.
She's dead.
[engine revving]
[revving continues]
[heavy metal music]
♪ I can't remember
what happened to me ♪
You guys need to
get out of here.
Let's get to Julia's.
Go!
[Max] Come on. Come on!
[dramatic music]
[tires squealing]
- [gunshots]
- [screaming]
[thud]
[tires screeching]
[heavy metal music playing]
♪ Sinister grin ♪
♪ Oh ♪
[Harper] Yes, sir.
Don't worry about that little
mishap at the cemetery earlier.
We're about to blow the roof
off this town with our plans.
[Julia] There were
two people killed.
That's terrible.
Okay, it's- it's bad.
I understand.
Those troubled individuals
gone too soon.
But last night's Grave Rave
was incredible.
And I could totally see it being
a fixture of this town
going forward.
Just like your museum is.
Wow.
Julia, this could
be huge financially.
For the town, for you,
for everybody.
Okay, let's just chat
in a couple of days, okay?
And get the ball rolling.
I'm thinking world wide web.
I'm thinking we do something
with the old Miller property.
I mean, this could be
the next Graceland, huh?
What do you say?
All right, let's just chat
in a couple days, okay?
Julia, I'm gonna head out
for the night.
Thank you, Ken.
I appreciate you.
- Get home safe.
- You too.
It's another home
run for us, mom.
You know what, Harper?
I'm exhausted.
I'm trying to process this.
They found two bodies
in the cemetery.
Mom, people die every day.
This is a huge win for us.
Are you listening to yourself?
Stop, okay?
Just stop. Stop!
Stop! I don't want
to hear it anymore.
Let's do a walk
through and go home.
Okay. Fine.
God damn it!
Fuck! Where are my
fucking keys?
God damn it!
[Max] Julia!
Please, you have to help us!
Please, please!
They're all dead! Please!
Okay. Calm down.
Can you please call the police?
What- what happened?
There was a guy in a mask,
he murdered everybody!
Okay, Quinn.
Where's your grandmother?
Where is she?
She's dead.
Oh my God.
Julia, can you please just
call the fucking police?
Okay! Okay, okay! Stay here.
Okay? Stay here!
[Harper] Brody?
You still here?
Yeah. Finishing the job, man.
It's all right, man.
You can get up out of here.
Mom's closing up shop.
All right.
I'll get right out of here.
Who the hell are you?
[blood spurting]
[urinating]
[choking]
[slicing]
[knocking]
Bathroom's occupied!
[insistent knocking]
[dramatic music]
No! Who are you?
No--
[splashing and coughing]
No!
[slicing]
Come on!
I called the cops!
You're gonna be all right!
Come with me!
It's gonna be okay!
Come up here!
Julia! Stay away from him!
[screaming] No!
No!
Get the fuck away from me!
No! [screaming]
[crunching]
[screaming]
[squelching]
Oh fuck!
[sinister music]
Quinn!
Fuck you!
[muffled voices]
[recording plays]
Deranged, depraved,
dismembered, deformed.
Guys, look!
[ominous music]
Oh my God!
Julia.
Goodman.
Call it in.
...Code Red.
It's him.
It's who?
It's my cousin.
God damn it, Chief.
The murders?
His mother's body is missing?
This is my cousin, I know it.
And where the hell
are you going?
To stop him!
[haunting vocalizing]
[vocalizing continues]
[gasps]
Oh, what...
What the fuck?
Max?
Max! Max!
- Oh, fuck! Shit!
- Oh, fuck!
[door creaks]
Oh, fuck.
I'm sorry I froze.
Oh, God, I'm so fucking useless.
Oh.
[winces]
Oh, God. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Quinn? Oh.
- Quinn? Quinny?
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
We've been watching these
movies since we were kids.
You know how it's
gonna end for me.
- You're the final girl.
- Oh, fuck off, Max.
Oh.
What is this fucking place?
[dramatic sting]
[clanking]
Act like you're still out.
[heavy footsteps]
[sniffs]
[tense music]
[stabbing]
Come on! We have to go!
Come on, come on!
[music intensifies]
[pulsing, tense music]
[boards clatter]
Quinn! Keep going.
Get out of here!
[tense music continues]
- [yelps]
- [thud]
Go go go go!
There! There!
[struggling]
[Max] I can't get it.
[snarling]
[screaming]
You fucking freak!
[thud]
Hey! Mama's boy!
[slicing]
[thud]
[landing blows]
[board clatters]
[music climaxes, clams]
[metal clangs]
- [Logan] Alex!
- [gunshot]
Colin, stop!
Just stop.
[haunting music]
Your mom wouldn't want this.
My aunt Marilyn.
She wouldn't want this.
Put the axe down, buddy.
[axe clatters]
Hey.
We're the only family we got.
- [stabbing]
- [gasps]
[blood dripping]
[groans]
[tense music]
No!
[choking]
[heavy heartbeats]
[heartbeats slowing]
[screaming]
[coughing]
[blood splattering]
[music climaxes, calms]
[panting]
[squelching]
[haunting music]
[dry chuckling]
[laughing]
I'll come back for you.
I'm changing the narrative.
[blood spurting]
[heavy rock music]
[Boy] Where's the boy
from below?
The sad, tormented,
vengeful soul.
Run, if you may.
Escape him, you might.
His curse will continue
on Halloween night.
♪ In the back of my mind
at all times ♪
♪ I drive through
complete wonderment ♪
♪ I wanna feel,
I wanna express ♪
♪ I've got the awareness
of death ♪
♪ We are shadows
with borrowed breath ♪
♪ I've got the awareness
of death ♪
♪ Give everything
until the end ♪
♪ Find more when you think
you have nothing left ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ The awareness of death ♪
♪ In the night
I gasped for air ♪
♪ It's like I'm being prepared
for when it isn't there ♪
♪ Breaching the surface again,
only to dive back in ♪
♪ I wanna feel,
I wanna express ♪
♪ I've got the awareness
of death ♪
♪ We are shadows
with borrowed breath ♪
♪ I've got the awareness
of death ♪
♪ In the back of my mind
at all times resides ♪
♪ the awareness of death ♪
♪ In the back of my mind ♪
♪ At all times I drive through
complete wonderments ♪
♪ In the back of my mind ♪
♪ At all times resides
the awareness of death ♪
♪ In the back of my mind ♪
♪ At all times I drive
through complete wonderment ♪
♪ I wanna feel,
I wanna express ♪
♪ I've got the awareness
of death ♪
♪ We are shadows
with borrowed breath ♪
♪ I've got the awareness
of death ♪
♪ Give everything
until the end ♪
♪ Find more when you think
you have nothing left ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ The awareness of death ♪
♪ [haunting synth music] ♪